http://www.delrionewsherald.com/site/privacy.html

MLB
Soccer ( FIFA )
Del Rio Grande
Southern Newspapers Inc., owner of The Del Rio News-Herald and www.delrionewsherald.com, is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using our web site and related online services.This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit or subscribe to the site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal information received by Southern Newspapers Inc. in connection with your subscriptions to the print edition of The Del Rio News-Herald.We may make content or services from other Web sites partnered with The Del Rio News-Herald available to you from links located on www.delrionewsherald.com. These other sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such site to determine how that site protects your privacy.Information we collectGeneral: When you register, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your computers, profession, investing habits and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit the site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our sites, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each page, and the length of their visits.How we use information collectedWe may use information in the following ways:For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions or registrations.To send you notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.We may combine the information that we collect from you on the site with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products, services and sites. Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of Southern Newspapers Inc. unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us.Compliance with legal processWe may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary tocomply with the law or with legal process;protect and defend our rights and property;protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web sites;protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Subscriber Agreement or Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights).Online advertisingWhen you view an ad, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The information collected is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts.Comments and questionsIf you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at support@delrionewsherald.com.
Today's e-Edition
Del Rio News-Herald
Del Rio News-Herald
Latest News
California's health order falling on many deaf ears
Bhutan lawmakers vote to decriminalize same-sex relations
Akers runs wild, Newton benched as Rams rout Patriots 24-3
Texas Rio Grande Valley tops Texas A&M-CC 68-64
Shuler scores 23; Ole Miss beats Jackson St. 80-45 in opener
Robbins has 27 points as Minnesota beats Kansas City 90-61
Cuba's president to drop its dual currency system Jan. 1
Vincent Davis rushes for 247 yards, Pitt beats Ga Tech 34-20
No. 20 Syracuse women beat Miami 69-58 in ACC opener
Wilson, Pitts help No. 10 Texas A&M women beat UALR 79-56
